<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<StoryVillageQuestName>Caravan Adventures - Visit a friend</StoryVillageQuestName>
	<StoryVillageQuestDesc_delete>{0} invited you to visit her in the nearest {1}'s village {2}. \nShe greatly enjoyed her stay back when at your colony and can't wait to see the gang again.</StoryVillageQuestDesc_delete>
	<StoryVillageQuestDesc>{0} sent a letter requesting help urgently. The letter reads:\n</StoryVillageQuestDesc>
	<StoryVillageQuestLetterContent>Dear {0},\n\nI really hope u get this letter in time, or we might all be dead. We came across a large shrine and as we cracked it open masses of mechanoids streamed out. We got away, but eversince huge hordes of mechanoids keep attacking our village.\nI'm sending this letter in hope that you can make it here in time to assist us. We're preparing an escape, but we have to wait for our reinforcements to stand any chance of escaping with our lifes.\n\nPlease help us in those dark times, we'd never forget this great deed.</StoryVillageQuestLetterContent>
	<StoryVillageQuestLetterContentPS>PS: I hope you guys are doing well, i really miss talking to you, i had such a great time when we met. I hope to see you soon, aiding us again.</StoryVillageQuestLetterContentPS>
	<StoryVillageQuestLetterContentEnding>Your's sincerly,\n\n{0}\n</StoryVillageQuestLetterContentEnding>
	<VisitStoryVillageLabel>Enter {0}</VisitStoryVillageLabel>
	<StoryVillageEnterMapMessage>Entering village</StoryVillageEnterMapMessage>
	<StoryVillageArrivedLetterTitle>Entered {0}</StoryVillageArrivedLetterTitle>
	<StoryVillageArrivedLetterMessage>Your caravan arrived at {0}. Seems to be a nice place.</StoryVillageArrivedLetterMessage>
	
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_DiaTitle>{0} embraces you</StoryVillage_Dia1_DiaTitle>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_1>Oh, hey {0}, i didn't expect a visit from you, at least not in these times...</StoryVillage_Dia1_1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_1_Option1>That's quite the warm welcome...</StoryVillage_Dia1_1_Option1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_2>Uh, no, you got me wrong here. I'm glad you are here, but we've been under constant attacks by mechs from a nearby site.
	\nAnother attack is immenent and we may have to flee and give up the village. Our forward outlooks described a huge army lead by some mechanical nightmare!
	\nYou should leave, you're in danger here.</StoryVillage_Dia1_2>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option1>Nah, don't give up so fast, we'll save the village together</StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option2>Alright, we're outa here, wish you the best</StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option2>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_3>Oh look, there they come, take cover!\n\nMy god, what a horde...</StoryVillage_Dia1_3>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_3_Option1>Are you really sure you want to fight this?</StoryVillage_Dia1_3_Option1>

	<StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_MechsArrived>Either help {0} to defend their base or make a run for it, tho they would make good allies in the battles to come</StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_MechsArrived>
	<VillageAttackMechsMessage>{0} are attacking {2}</VillageAttackMechsMessage>

	<StoryVillage_Dia2_Title>{0} shouts loudly...</StoryVillage_Dia2_Title>
	<StoryVillage_Dia2_1>Ey, our reinforcements are here, lets go guys, give them hell!</StoryVillage_Dia2_1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia2_1_Option1>This isn't gonna end well...</StoryVillage_Dia2_1_Option1>

	<StoryVillage_Dia3_Title>{0} calls out to you...</StoryVillage_Dia3_Title>
	<StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Alive>I got out alive, this is horrible. I'll have to meet up with our expert hunters and come up with a plan how to defeat these things.\nWe need to act fast or all is lost.\nI'll contact you when we know more, good luck.\n... and thanks. I won't forget that you fought for us.</StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Alive>
	<StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Dying>Save... urself...\nThis battle... is lost...\nSomeone will reach... out to... you...</StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Dying>
	<StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Option1>Lets move on</StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Option1>
	<StoryVillage_SacHunters_Fleeing>Story Hunters are fleeing.</StoryVillage_SacHunters_Fleeing>

	<StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_Survived>You survivded and made it out alive. But where did all those mechs come from? Best to watch out for more clues...</StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_Survived>
</LanguageData>

