<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<StoryVillageQuestName>Caravan Adventures - Rescue a friend</StoryVillageQuestName>
	<StoryVillageQuestDesc>{0} sent a letter requesting help urgently. The letter reads:\n</StoryVillageQuestDesc>
	<StoryVillageQuestLetterContent>Dear {0},\n\nI really hope u get this letter in time, or we might all be dead. We came across a large shrine and as we cracked it open masses of mechanoids streamed out. We got away, but eversince huge hordes of mechanoids keep attacking our village.\nI'm sending this letter in hope that you can make it here in time to assist us. We're preparing an escape, but we have to wait for our reinforcements to stand any chance of escaping with our lifes.\n\nPlease help us in those dark times and venture to {1} at haste, we'd never forget this great deed.</StoryVillageQuestLetterContent>
	<StoryVillageQuestLetterContentPS>PS: I hope you guys are doing well, i really miss talking to you, i had such a great time when we met. I hope to see you soon, aiding us again.</StoryVillageQuestLetterContentPS>
	<StoryVillageQuestLetterContentEnding>Your's sincerly,\n\n{0}\n</StoryVillageQuestLetterContentEnding>
	<StoryVillageQuestDesc2>Travel to the {0} Village {1} and assist {2} before it's too late.</StoryVillageQuestDesc2>
	<VisitStoryVillageLabel>Enter {0}</VisitStoryVillageLabel>
	<StoryVillageEnterMapMessage>Entering village</StoryVillageEnterMapMessage>
	<StoryVillageArrivedLetterTitle>Entered {0}</StoryVillageArrivedLetterTitle>
	<StoryVillageArrivedLetterMessage>Your caravan arrived at {0}. Seems to be a nice place.</StoryVillageArrivedLetterMessage>
	
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_DiaTitle>{0} embraces you</StoryVillage_Dia1_DiaTitle>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_1>{0}, you came. Thank god. We barely fended off the last attack and our scouts spotted the next and yet biggest army only a few minutes away.\n\nI hope our reinforcements make it in time. </StoryVillage_Dia1_1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_1_Option1>Good to see you. Any idea why those mechs are after you that bad?\nWe sure get attacked aswell, but nothing as you described.</StoryVillage_Dia1_1_Option1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_2>[{0}, pale and exhausted, looks you in the eyes] We don't know exactly. It was a huge shrine. Once we discovered the hordes of mechs coming out of that place we used our last nuke to level the whole place. But it looks like most made it out and they're after us now.\n\n[{0} hands you a small device in haste] Take this comms device, so i'll be able to contact you.</StoryVillage_Dia1_2>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option1>Alright, lets see if we can't defend this place.</StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option2>How about we just leave now?</StoryVillage_Dia1_2_Option2>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_3>They are here, take cover!\n\n[{0} screamed] My god, what a horde...</StoryVillage_Dia1_3>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_3_Option1>Are you really sure you want to fight this?</StoryVillage_Dia1_3_Option1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_4>Yah, they need to be held of until we were able to get the civilians out of here.</StoryVillage_Dia1_4>
	<StoryVillage_Dia1_4_Option1>Guess today is as good a day to die as any.</StoryVillage_Dia1_4_Option1>
	
	<StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_MechsArrived>Either help {0} to defend {1} base or make a run for it, although Sacrileg Hunters would make good allies in the battles to come.</StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_MechsArrived>
	<VillageAttackMechsMessage>{0} are attacking {2}</VillageAttackMechsMessage>

	<StoryVillage_Dia2_Title>{0} shouts loudly...</StoryVillage_Dia2_Title>
	<StoryVillage_Dia2_1>Ey, our reinforcements are here, lets go guys, give them hell!\n\nTowns people and council members, to the escape routes!</StoryVillage_Dia2_1>
	<StoryVillage_Dia2_1_Option1>This isn't gonna end well...</StoryVillage_Dia2_1_Option1>

	<StoryVillage_Dia3_Title>{0} contacts you via comms device...</StoryVillage_Dia3_Title>
	<StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Alive>We got out alive, this is horrible. I'll have to meet up with our expert hunters and come up with a plan how to defeat these things. We need to act fast or all is lost.\n\nI'll contact you when we know more, good luck.\n... and thanks. I won't forget that you fought for us.</StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Alive>
	<StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Dying>Save... urself...\nThis battle... is lost...\nSomeone will reach... out to... you... i'm... sorry...</StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Dying>
	<StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Option1>Lets move on</StoryVillage_Dia3_1_Option1>
	<StoryVillage_SacHunters_Fleeing>Sacrileg Hunters are fleeing.</StoryVillage_SacHunters_Fleeing>
	<StoryVillage_SacHuntersCivs_Fleeing>Villagers are escaping as planned.</StoryVillage_SacHuntersCivs_Fleeing>

  <StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_CanLeaveSuccess>The towns folk was able to get to safety, your task is complete.</StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_CanLeaveSuccess>
  <StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_CanLeaveFailed>Sacrileg Hunter's leadership took losses and they will need some time to recovert. Your task failed.</StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_CanLeaveFailed>
	<StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_Survived>You survivded and made it out alive. But where did all those mechs come from? Best to watch out for more clues...</StoryVillage_QuestUpdate_Survived>
</LanguageData>

