<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Caravan Adventures [Beta]</name>
	<author>iforgotmysocks</author>
	<url></url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <packageId>iforgotmysocks.CaravanAdventures</packageId>
	<description>
[Beta 0.3.0]

Welcome to the beta for Caravan Adventures. As always, please backup your savegames. I'm glad for any feedback and bugs you may find or can provide. :)
The release will be published as a new workshop file while this beta will remain unlisted and will eventually be removed, so please don't waste your hard earned steam points on the beta version.
Caravan Adventures aims to transform traveling around the world into a fun adventure by providing new features to replace the annoying micromanagement, make traveling more fun and give you a sense of purpose doing so. Quick heads-up, about 25% of this mod's content is the Storyline, which requires Royalty. Everything else can be used without it, don't worry.

Please invite new people to our Discord (https://discord.gg/KwaRubs2kx) instead of just sharing this mod link, as i prefer beta feedback there. Thanks guys!
All mod details available in the Mod's Wiki (https://github.com/iforgotmysocks/CaravanAdventuresWiki/wiki)

Automatic Camp Setup
* Settle on tiles by having ur pawns set up a camp first, before you even get involved.
* If you prepared and have enough spacer tent supplies, you will be able to stay in high quality camp sites, if not, ur pawns will divert to make shift materials.
* You pawns automatically build enough tents for your individual number of travelers and prisoners. Pawns also choose their tents based on their relationship.
* Choose to either leave the bulk of most items strapped to your animals or create enough storage tents, so all your equipment is tugged away "savely".
* Choose to preapply basic jobs, like creating a set of fresh clothes, butcher animals or grill some stakes
* Leave the camp site immediately if you want to, just for the impatient ones

Caravan forming / trading presets
* Set up 3 presets in mod settings, that allow you to quickly select all items for travel, or create specific trade filters to select all you may want to sell at once.
* More basic selection options for all items or none
* Keep the automatic supplies disabled with a toggle, to avoid some lag when it's active everytime you open up the dialog

Mechanoid Bounty
* Initialy part of the story, but also seperately available
* Hunt mechanoids to receive bounty credits with the faction that called out the bounty
* Get assistance from said faction on any map you currently have pawns located (they can help engage hostile locations)
* Hire veteran soldiers for a hefty large amount of bounty credits, which come with alot of experience and u're able to choose some of their traits
* Purchase valuable items in exchange for bounty credits
* Improve relations to other factions in exchange for bounty credits
* Buy bounty credits for a large amount of silver

Immersion - Travel companions
* Pawns start out disliking the newcomers due to uncertainty and some lack of trust
* Pawns indiviually bond with eath other over time which can turn the initial distrust into a true friendship

Caravan Incidents
* More smaller events that do not always have to end in a fight (currently only 1)

Storyline (requires Royalty)
* A storyline that gives you a reason to travel the world
* Form a bond with a new faction sharing your troubles on a new world
* Encounter a dangerous threat that endangers the entire world
* Fight bosses to claim treasures, learn powerful spells and prevent the end of all living beings

(All categories can be enabled or disabled and further configured to your liking in the mod's settings)


Credits

Artwork:
Artwork and the preview image generously provided by Shakesthespeare, thank you mate, u're awesome!
Portal in Ancient master shrine by gecko-kobold

Sounds:
Anima tree whisper by zapsplat (zapsplat_whispers.mp3) from https://www.zapsplat.com
Earthquake by zatar (zatar_earthquake.mp3) https://freesound.org/people/zatar/sounds/514381/
slice1 by audione https://freesound.org/people/audione/sounds/52458/
slice2 by freefire66 https://freesound.org/people/freefire66/sounds/175949/
slice3 by TheBuilder15 https://freesound.org/people/TheBuilder15/sounds/434896/
slice4 by Aleks41 https://freesound.org/people/Aleks41/sounds/449552/

CE Patch done by dokupe / the english mech hater

Thanks to the testers who helped to get this mod on the road!

  </description>
</ModMetaData>
